Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. William Woodville Rockhill papers (MS Am 2121): Guide.
William Woodville Rockhill papers,
- I. Correspondence and other papers
  - Martin, W D P A.L.s.(W.D.P.Martin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 29 Oct [1894], (1640a); ([4]p.)
  - Marvin, George. A.L.s.(George Marvin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 190-?], (1641); ([4]p.)
  - Marvin, George. A.L.s.(George Marvin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 19 Jul 1908., (1642); ([4]p.)
  - Mason, Frank H. Typed L.s.(Frank H. Mason) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Frankfort-on-the Main, 11 Oct 1895., (1643); 4l.
  - Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908. A.L.s.(O. Mason) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 17 Dec 1891., (1644); [2]p.
  - Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908. Typed L.s.(O. Mason) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 13 Oct 1893., (1645); 1l.
  - Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908. Typed L.s.(O.T.Mason) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 25 Oct [1897]., (1645a); 2l.
  - Mason, Otis Tufton, 1838-1908. Typed L.s.(O. Mason) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 26 Apr [1898]., (1646); 2l.
  - Mason, William Powell. A.L.s.(W. Powell Mason) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Boston, 31 Mar [n.d.], (1647); ([3]p.)
  - Maunoir, C. A.L.s.(C.Maunoir) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 19 Oct 1890., (1647a); ([4]p.)
  - Maunoir, C. A.L.s.(C.Maunoir) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 18 Nov 1890., (1647b); ([3]p.)
  - Mannoir, C. A.L.s.(C. Mannoir) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 3 Feb 1891., (1648); ([4]p.)
  - Mendenhall, Thomas Corwin, 1841-1924. A.L.s.(T. C. Mendenhall) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 10 Apr [1894]., (1649); ([3]p.)
  - Mercantile beneficial association. A.L.s.(Saml. Clarke, President, Mer. Ben. Assn.) to the family of Abram C. Rockhill; Philadelphia, 10 Apr 1859., (1650); ([1]p.)
  - Merrill, Henry F. A.L.s.(H. F. Merrill) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Wuhu, 24 Mar 1901., (1651); ([3]p.)
  - Metropolitan club. Washington. Ms.L.s.(Arnold Hague, Secretary) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 5 Nov 1895., (1652); ([1]p.)
  - Meyer, Frank Nicholas. A.L.s.(Frank N. Meyer) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Hoi Ryong, 4 Sep [1906]., (1653); 3l.
  - Meyer, Frank Nicholas. A.L.s.(Frank N. Meyer) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Tai yuan fu, 6 May [1907]., (1654); 3l.
  - Meyer, Frank Nicholas. A.L.s.(Frank N. Meyer) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Caucasus, 28 Feb 1910., (1655); 3l.
  - Meyer, Frank Nicholas. A.L.s.(Frank N. Meyer) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Tiflis, 2 Apr 1910., (1656); 4l.
  - Michael, William H. A.L.s.(Wm. H. Michael) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 4 Jun 1906., (1657); ([4]p.)
  - Michaelis, Otho Ernest. A.L.s.(Otho Frnest Michaelis) to [Edith (Howell) Perkins)] Rockhill; El Paso, 10 Jan 1915., (1658); ([4]p.)
  - Mill, Eugh Robert, 1861- A.L.s.(Hugh Robert Mill) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 31 Mar 1898., (1659); ([3]p.)
  - Millard, de [ ? ] A.L.s.(deMillard) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Lyon, 28 Jan 1884., (1659a); ([2]p.)
  - Millard, de [ ? ] A.L.s.(deMillard) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Lyon, 3 Feb 1884., (1659b); ([2]p.)
    In French. Enclosure: A.L.s.(deMillard) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; Lyon, 24 Jan 1884. ([3]p.) In French.
  - Miller, P. A.L.s.(P. Miller) to the family of the late Mr. Thomas C. Rockhill; Bolivar, 26 Apr 1855., (1660); 1l.
  - Miller, R. S. A.L.s.(R. S. Miller) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 18 Dec 1909., (1661); ([3]p.)
  - Miller, R. S. Telegram s.(Miller) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 1913., (1662); 1l.
  - Millingen, Alexander van. A.L.s.(A. van Millingen) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Robert College, 7 Jun 1912., (1663); ([2]p.)
  - Moir, John K. A.L.s.(J. K. Moir) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 14 Jun 1905., (1664); 1l.
  - Moir, John. K. A.L.s.(J. K. Moir) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 25 Jul 1905., (1665); 2l.
  - Moir, John K. A. Memorandum s.(J. K. Moir) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 25 Jul 1905., (1666); 1l.
  - Moir, John K. Typed L.s.(John K. Moir) to Chang Chi Tung; Shanghai, 14 Jul 1905., (1667); ([2]p.)
  - Moncheur, Ludovic, baron, 1857- Typedscript of L.s.(Moncheur) to [John] Hay; Warm Springs, 13 Aug 1904., (1668); 1l.
  - Moody, William Henry, 1853-1916. Typed L.s.(W. H. Moody) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 6 Apr 1900., (1669); 1l.
  - Moore, Beverly K. Typed L.s.(Beverly K. Moore) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Boston, 8 Feb 1900., (1670); 1l.
  - Moore, Charles Forrest. A.L.s.(C. F. Moore) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 188-?], (1671); ([2]p.)
    Enclosure: A. Notes (unsigned); [n.p., n.d.] 1l. Also: Ms. in Thibetian.
  - Moore, Charles Forrest. A.L.s.(C. F. Moore) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 3 Feb [1885]. folde4, (1672); ([2]p.)
  - Moore, John Bassett. A.L.s.(J. B. Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 6 Mar 1895., (1673); 1l.
  - Moore, John Bassett, A.L.s.(J.B.Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 20 Apr 1895., (1673a); ([3]p.)
  - Moore, John Bassett A.L.s.(J.B.Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 3 Oct 1895., (1673b); ([4]p.)
  - Moore, John Bassett. Typed L.s.(J. B. Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 6 Feb 1896., (1674); 1l.
  - Moore, John Bassett. A.L.s.(J. B. Moore) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 10 Feb 1896., (1675); 1l.
  - Moore, John Bassett. A.L.s.(J. B. Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 17 Feb 1896., (1676); 1l.
  - Moore, John Bassett. A.L.s.(J. B. Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 20 May 1898., (1677); ([1]p.)
  - Moore, John Bassett. Typed L.s.(J. B. Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 25 Jun 1903., (1678); 1l.
  - Moore, John Bassett. A.L.s.(J. B. Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 12 Oct 1903., (1679); 1l.
  - Moore, John Bassett. A.L.s.(J. B. Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 12 Oct 1904., (1680); 1l.
  - Moore, John Bassett. Typed L.s.(J. B. Moore) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 28 Aug 1913., (1681); 1l.
  - Moors, Henry Jay, 1854- Typed L.s.(H. J. Moors) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Apia Samea, 22 Mar 1898., (1682); 1l.
  - Moors, Henry Jay, 1854- Typed L.s.(H. J. Moors) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Apia Samea, 10 Aug 1898., (1683); 1l.
  - Moors, Henry Jay, 1854- A.L.s.(H. B. Moors) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 15 Feb 1907., (1684); 3l.
  - Moors, Henry Jay, 1854- A.L.s.(H. J. Moors) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 28 Feb 1907., (1685); ([2]p.)
  - Morey, Cephas. Ms. Articles of Agreement s.(Cephas Morey: William L. Newbold); [Philadelphia] 25 Jun 1835., (1686); ([3]p.)
  - Morgan, E. Delmar. A.L.s.(E. Delmar Morgan) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 14 Oct 1891., (1687); ([3]p.)
  - Morgan, E.Delmar. A.L.s.(E. Delmar Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 2 Jan 1895., (1688); ([4]p.)
  - Morgan, E. Delmar. A.L.s.(E. Delmar Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 7 Mar 1895., (1689); ([4]p.)
  - Morgan, E. Delmar. A.L.s.(E. Delmar Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 3 Jun 1895., (1690); ([1]p.)
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. Typed L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Yokohama, 26 Apr 1904., (1691); 6l.
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. Typed L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 4 Jun 1904., (1692); 7l.
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. Typed L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 18 Jun 1904., (1693); 5l.
    Enclosed: Typescript of Report s.(G. Hayashi) to "Dear Mr. Straight"; Seoul, Coree, 7 Jun 1904. 2l.
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. A.L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 6 Jul 1904., (1694); ([20]p.)
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. A.L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 2 Jul 1904., (1695); ([12]p.)
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. A.L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Newchang, 28 Jul 1904., (1696); ([16]p.)
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. Typed L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 12 Jul 1905., (1697); 5l.
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. A.L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 17 Aug [1905], (1698); ([6]p.)
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. A.L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 29 Aug [1905], (1699); ([8]p.)
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. A.L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill;[n.p.] 17 Nov 1905., (1700); ([4]p.)
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. A.L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 21 Nov 1905., (1701); ([8]p.)
  - Morgan, Edwin Vernon, 1865-1934. A.L.s.(Edwin Morgan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Rio de Janeiro, 2 Jan 1915., (1702); ([4]p.)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, 1856- Typed L.s.(H. Morgenthau) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Constantinople, 28 Nov 1913., (1703); 1l.
  - Morice, Eugene L. A.L.s.(E. L. Morice) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 16 May 1911., (1704); ([2]p.)
    Enclosed: Printed corrected invoice filled out in ms. to W[illiam] W[oodville] Rockhill; London, 16 May 1911. 1l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 20 Dec 1904., (1705); ([12]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New Castle, 26 Aug [1905]., (1706); 10l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 1 Jul [1905]., (1707); ([2]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest. 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; S.S. Tartar, 27 Jul 1905., (1708); ([4]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 20 Jun [1907]., (1709); 2l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typescript of "Final Protocol"; Rome, 26 May 1907., (1710); 1l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill;[London] 30 Oct 1907., (1711); ([4]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill;[London] 9 Nov 1907., (1712); ([3]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 19 Dec [1909]., (1713); ([8]p.)
  - Morrison, George Erhest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 17 Feb 1910., (1714); ([4]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill;[London] 31 Aug 1910., (1715); ([8]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill;[London] 13 Sep 1910., (1716); ([2]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 11 Oct 1910., (1717); ([2]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [London] 14 Feb 1911., (1718); 1l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 28 Mar 1911., (1719); 2l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G E.Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 25 Apr 1911., (1719a); 2l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 8 Jun 1911., (1720); 4l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 9 Aug 1911., (1721); 1l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 9 Feb 1912., (1722); 1l.
    Postscript in his autograph.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G.E.Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 15 Mar 1912., (1722a); 3l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 3 Apr 1912., (1723); 1l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 10 May 1912., (1724); 2l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. A.L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Pei tu ho, 9 Jul 1912., (1725); ([3]p.)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Letter to [William Woodville] Rockhill; 29 Jul 1913., (1725a)
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 28 Oct 1912., (1726); 1l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed L.s.(G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 9 Dec 1913., (1727); 1l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1920. Typed (c.c.) L.s. (G. E. Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 23 Dec 1913., (1728); 1l.
  - Morrison, George Ernest, 1862-1930 Typed L.s.(G.E.Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 4 Feb 1914., (1728a); 2l.
    Enclosure: Typed "Translation of Memo"...; Urga, 29 Dec 1913. 3l. With autograph emendations. Also: Ms. in Chinese, with a red cover. And: Ms. in Mongolian [?].
  - Morrison, Thomas. Typed L.s.(Thomas Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 12 Aug 1909., (1729); 1l.
  - Morrison, Thomas. A.L.s.(Thomas Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 9 Sep 1913., (1730); ([1]p.)
  - Morrison, Thomas. Typed L.s.(Thomas Morrison) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 26 Jun 1914., (1731); 2l.
  - Morse, Edward Sylvester, 1838-1925. A.L.s.(Edw. Morse) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Salem, 21 Apr [1885], (1732); ([2]p.)
  - Mueller, Herbert, 1885- A.L.s.(Herbert Mueller) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Berlin, 29 Feb [1908]., (1733); ([4]p.)
  - Mueller, Herbert, 1885- A.L.s.(Herbert Mueller) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Berlin, 12 Aug [1908]., (1734); ([4]p.)
  - Mueller, Herbert, 1885- A.L.s.(Herbert Mueller) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Berlin, 8 Nov 1908., (1735); ([4]p.)
  - Muffat, H A.L.s.(Muffot H.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Catrienlau, 15 May [1893]., (1735a); ([4]p.)
  - Muffot, H. A.L.s.(Muffot H.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Catsienlou, 29 May [1894]., (1735b); ([5]p.)
  - Mulligan, James H. A.L.s.(James H. Mulligan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Apia, Samoa, 12 Jul 1895., (1736); ([7]p.)
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. A.L.s.(A. Mumm) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking, 190-?], (1737); ([1]p.)
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. A.L.s.(A. Mumm) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking, 190-?], (1738); ([3]p.)
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. A.L.s.(A. Mumm) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking] 9 Aug [190-?], (1739); ([4]p.)
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. A.L.s.(A. M.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking, 190-?], (1740); ([3]p.)
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. A.L.s.(A. Mumm) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking, 190-?] ([3], (1741); p.
    )
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. A.L.s.(A. Mumm) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 3 May 1901., (1742); ([2]p.)
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. Ms.L.s.(A. Mumm) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 1 Feb 1902., (1743); ([2]p.)
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. Typescript s.(Mumm) to [?]; Peking, 27 May 1902., (1744); 1l.
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. A.L.s.(A. Mumm) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 31 Jan [1905]., (1745); ([4]p.)
  - Mumm, Arnold Louis. A.L.s.(A. Mumm) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Peitaiho, 29 Aug [1905], (1746); ([7]p.)
  - Munier, Louis H. Typed L.s.(Louis H. Munier) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Geneva, [1913], (1747); 1l.
  - Munier, Louis H. Printed calling card with autograph annotation; [Jun 1913], (1748); [2]p.
  - Murphy, George H. A.L.s.(George H. Murphy) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Luxemburg, 14 Nov 1895., (1749); ([1]p.)
  - Muster, Fr. de A.L.s.(Fr.deMuster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Lanchu, 19 Feb [189-?], (1749a); ([3]p.)
  - Muster, Fr. de A.L.s.(Fr. de Muster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Lanchu fu 9 Sep 1894., (1749b); ([5]p.)
  - Muster, Fr. de A.L.s.(Fr. deMuster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Lanchu fu, 14 Jan 1895., (1749c); ([4]p.)
  - Muster, Fr. de A.L.s.(Fr.de Muster) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Lan chu, 17 Jan 1896., (1749d); ([8]p.)
  - Nairn, C. J. Typed L.s.(C. J. Nairn) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chefoo, 19 Jul 1905., (1750); 1l.
  - National geographic society. Typed L.s.(Henry Gannett, Secretary) to [William] [Woodville]Rockhill; Washington, 21 Apr 1890., (1751); ([1]p.)
  - Neale, S C Typed L.s.(S.C.Neale) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 2 Jul 1897., (1751a); 1l.
  - Nealy, Sid H. A.L.s.(Sid H. Nealy) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 24 Dec 1903., (1752); 5l.
  - Nealy, Sid H. A.L.s.(Sid H. Nealy) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 31 Jul 1904., (1753); 4l.
  - Nelson, Henry Loomis, 1846-1908. Typed L.s.(H. O. Nelson) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Franklin, Square, 9 Jul 1895., (1754); ([1]p.)
  - Newcomb, Simon, 1835-1909. Typed L.s.(S. Newcomb) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 12 Feb 1904., (1755); 2l.
  - Nicholas II, Czar of Russia, 1868-1918. Transcript of "Substance of full powers of the Russian Plenipotentaries"; [n.p.] 2 Jul [?], (1756); 2l.
  - Nicholas II, Czar of Russia, 1868-1918. Typescript of "Russian Imperial Ukaz"; [n.p.] 20 Jul / 2 Aug 1901., (1757); ([4]p.)
  - Nicholas II, Czar of Russia, 1868-1918. Typed "Direction des Ceremonies"; [n.p.] 27 Dec / 9 Jan 1909-1910., (1758); ([1]p.)
  - Nicholas II, Czar of Russia, 1868-1918. Printed invitation filled out in ms. to William Woodville Rockhill; [n.p.] 3 Dec 1910., (1759); 1l.
  - Nicholas II, Czar of Russia, 1868-1918. Printed invitation filled out in ms. to William Woodville Rockhill; [n.p., n.d.], (1760); 1l.
  - Nightingale, Henry Oscar. Typescript of Article entitled "Procuring the Dragon's Pool Tea Seed" s. (Henry Oscar Nightingale); Foochow, 8 Nov 1909., (1761); 16l.
    Enclosure: Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(Samuel L. Gracey) to David Fairchild; Foochow, 9 Nov 1909. 3l.
  - Nishikori, Sanzo. A.L.s.(Sanzo Nixhikori) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill and [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Yokohama, 21 Dec 1909., (1762); ([3]p.)
  - Nishikori, Sanzo. A.L.s.(Sanzo Nishikori) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill and [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Yokohama, 8 Jun 1914., (1763); ([4]p.)
  - Nicolopoulo, Panagiotis D. A.L.s.(P. D. Nicolopoulo) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Patriarcert, 24 Oct 1912., (1764); ([3]p.)
    InFrench.
  - Noyes, Laverne, 1849-1919. Typed L.s.(Laverne W. Noyes) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Chicago, 5 Aug 1909., (1765); 1l.
  - O'Brien, Thomas J. Typed L.s.(T. J. O'Brien) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Tokyo, 23 Jan 1909., (1766); 1l.
  - O'Brien, Thomas J. Typed L.s.(T. J. O'Brien) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Rome, 8 Jun 1912., (1767); 4l.
  - O'Brien, Thomas J. Typed L.s.(T. J. O'Brien) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Rome, 20 Jun 1912., (1768); 4l.
  - O'Brien, Thomas J. Typed L.s.(T. J. O'Brien) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Rome, 11 Jul 1912., (1769); 2l.
  - O'Brien, Thomas J. Typed L.s.(T. J. O'Brien) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Rome, 12 Jul 1912. Enclosure: Typescript Translation of Telegram appearing in newspapers, "L'Italia"., (1770)
  - O'Brien, Thomas J. A.L.s.(T. J. O'Brien) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 19 Sep [1912]., (1771); 1l.
  - O'Brien, Thomas J. Typed L.s.(Thomas J. O'Brien) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Rome, 14 Jan 1913., (1772); 1l.
  - O'Brien, Thomas J. Typed L.s.(T. J. O'Brien) to William Woodville Rockhill; Rome, 3 May 1913., (1773); 1l.
  - O'Connor, Sir William Frederick, 1870- A.L.s.(W. F. O'Connor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 1 Dec [190-?], (1774); ([5]p.)
  - O'Connor, Sir William Frederick, 1870- A.L.s.(W. F. O'Connor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 20 Nov [1908]., (1775); ([4]p.)
  - O'Connor, Sir William Frederick, 1870- A.L.s.(W. F. O'Connor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 1 Dec [1908]., (1776); ([1]p.)
  - O'Connor, Sir William Frederick, 1870- A.L.s.(W. F. O'Connor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Calcutta, 10 Feb 1909., (1777); ([10]p.)
  - O'Connor, Sir William Frederick, 1870- A.L.s.(W. F. O'Connor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Calcutta, 20 Mar [1909]., (1778); ([4]p.)
  - O'Connor, Sir William Frederick, 1870- A.L.s.(W. F. O'Connor) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Baluchistan, 2 Dec [1909]., (1779); ([4]p.)
  - O'Connor, Sir William Frederick, 1870- A.L.s.(W. F. O'Connor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Meshed, 3 Jun 1910., (1780); ([8]p.)
  - O'Laughlin, John Callan, 1873- A.L.s.(Cal O'Laughlin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 7 Jul 1901., (1781); ([4]p.)
  - O'Laughlin, John Callan, 1873- A.L.s.(O'Laughlin) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; St. Petersbourg, 11 Apr 1904., (1782); ([5]p.)
  - O'Laughlin, John Callan, 1873- Typed L.s.(J. C. O'Laughlin) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 4 May 1913., (1783); 1l.
  - O'Laughlin, John Callan, 1873- A.L.s.(J. C. O'Laughlin) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 22 Sep 1913., (1784); ([1]p.)
  - O'Laughlin, John Callan, 1873- Typed L.s.(J. C. O'Laughlin) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 2 Oct 1913., (1785); 1l.
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 24 Sep [189-?], (1786); ([3]p.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. Ms. Copy of Telegram received s.(Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Boston, 18 Aug 189-?, (1787); 1l.
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 189-?], (1788); ([2]p.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 189-?], (1789); 2l.
    Enclosure: A. Draft (unsigned); [n.p., 189-?] 2l.
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 189-?], (1790); ([2]p.)
  - Olney, Rochard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington 24 Jul [1896], (1790a); (2l.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington 28 Jul [1896], (1790b); (2l.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.N.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington 29 Jul [ ? ], (1790c); (1l.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 31 Jul [1896], (1790d); ([3]p.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.N.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington 7 Aug [1896], (1790e); (1l.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. Typed L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Boston, 11 Aug 1896., (1790f); 1l.
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. Transcript of Telegram received s.(Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Falmouth, 14 Aug 1896., (1791); 1l.
  - Olney, Rochard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 16 Aug [1896], (1791a); ([5]p.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington 19 Aug [1896], (1791b); ([6]p.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Boston, 22 Aug 1896., (1792); 1l.
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington 23 Aug [1896], (1792a); ([5]p.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington 9 Sep [1896], (1792b); ([7]p.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington 11 Sep [1896], (1792c); ([6]p.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. A.L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, [Sep 1896], (1793); ([2]p.)
  - Olney, Richard, 1835-1917. Typed L.s.(Richard Olney) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Boston, 15 Sep 1896., (1794); 1l.